ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Administration Program Files. (Box 78)
  - Teambuilding 06W036 NFTA - Oct. 5 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Upstate NY L/R Initiative 06W035 Public Program 8/3/06 Rebholz/Henderson/Scanza, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Lifestyle Management 06W034 UAW Ford NPC 8/21-8/25/06 Grogan, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Dealing With Seneca Nation of Indians 06W033 9/14/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Effective Interviewing 06W032 Seneca Nation of Indians 8/23/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - SHRM Information Session 06W031 Public 9/6/06 Lampen, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - WNY EEO HR Minority Network 06W030 8/4/2006 Henderson (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Resolving Conflict 06W028 Public 11/18-11/9/06 Lampen, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Fundamentals of Compensation 06W027 Public 11/14-11/15/16 Lampen, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Legal Issues for Managers 06W026 Public 10/26/06 Lampen, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Building + Managing EMP Relations 06W024 Public 9/26-9/27/06 Lampen, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Contemporary Leadership Part I 06W023 Public 9/18-9/20/06 Lampen Canceled (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Sexual Harassment Prevention 06W022 Avox Systems 7/11/06; 7/12/06; 7/13/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Responding Locally to a Global Economy 06W020B Public Program 8/9/06- Session 4 Fleron, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Fundamentals of Human Resource 06W025 Public 10/10-10/12/06 Lampen, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Module 4 06W016 A/B Erie County Medical Center Corp 9/26/04 - 11/14/06 10/4-11/29/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - SHRM Classroom 06W021/06FHR068BF01 Public Program 9/12/2006-11/28/2006 Lampen (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - SHRM on Line 06W018 Public 9/11/06-11/20/06 Lampen (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Responding Locally to a Global Economy 06W020A Public Program 7/12/2006 - Session 3 Fleron (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Employment Maintenance 06W019 UAW Ford NPC Lima 9/11/06-9/15/06 Fleron/ Suggs, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Hottest Place to be Cool 06W017 Champions Network 6/12-6/14/07 Grogan, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - AIS Program 06W014 UAW Ford NPC10/23-10/27/06 Suggs/ Fleron, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Module 306W015A/B Erie County Medical Center Corp 8/22/06 9/13/06 Rebholz, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - AIS Program 06W013 UAW Ford NPC 9/25-9/29/06 Suggs/Fleron, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - AIS Program 06W012 UAW Ford NPC 8/13-8/18/06 Suggs/Fleron, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - AIS Program 06W011 UAW Ford NPC 7/24-7/28/06 Suggs/ Fleron, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - AIS Program 06W010 UAW Ford NPC 7/17- 7/21/06 Suggs/ Fleron, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Public Sector:LR Law in NYS 06W009 Public 06FLR210BF01 11/14 - 11/15/06 Henderson Canceled, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Dynamics-LBR Negotiations 06W008 Public 06FLR302BF01 10/30/06 Henderson Canceled, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - L/M Strategies-Org Change 06W007 Public 06FLR306BF01 10/24/06 Henderson, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - Effective Coll Bargaining 06W006 Public 06FLR203BF01 11/9-10/06 Henderson, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - Prep for Coll Bargaining 06W005 Public 06FLR201BF01 11/7-8/06 Henderson, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - Effective... Environment 06W004 Public 06FLR101BF01 10/11+12 Henderson, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 47)
- Administration Program Files. (Box 79)
  - Paychecks and Politics in America Public Program 1/30/06 05W034 Johnson, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Steward Training Public Program 1/9/06 05W033 Johnson, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Understanding Diversity + Workplace Hara. Boilmakers 05W041 9/8/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Labor Unions = The News Media Public Program 05W040 5/17/06 Johnson Cancelled, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining for Health Care Benefits Public Program 05W032 11/30/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Advancing the Union Sector Public Program 05W031 11/4/2005 Johnson (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Common Sense Economics Public Program 05W030 10/26/05 Johnson Canceled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration: Basics of Advocacy Public Program 05W029 10/17/2005 Johnson (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - The Taylor Law + PERB Public Program 05W028 10/17 + 10/19/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration: Basics of Advocacy Public Program 05W027 9/24/05 Johnson Cancelled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - SK Tour of Perry's Ice Cream 05W026 Cornell University- Ithaca 9/2/05 Wheaton, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - International Visitors Leadership 05W025 WorlConnect 8/25/05 Wheaton, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - SHRM Information Sesson 05W018B Public Program 8/2/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - SHRM Information Sesson 05W018A Public Program 8/2/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Effective Discipline 05W024 Niagara Housing Authority 9/16/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Thomson Publisher Review Survey 05W021B Thomson Business + Economics Publishing 7/6/05-7/10/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Thomson Publisher Review Survey 05W021A Thomson Business + Economics Publishing 7/11/05-7/20/05 Rebholz (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Applying Lean Tools 05W022 Cornell U - NYC Office 11/15-11/16/05 Wheaton, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - An Intro to Lean Principles 05W021 Cornell U - NYC Office 10/6/05 Wheaton, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Dev. Exemplary Leaders 05W020 Account Solutions Group 6/24; 7/8; 8/4; 8/18; TBD Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Public Sector Labor Relations Law 05W017 Public Program 11/15-11/16/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Prep for Collective Bargaining 05W016 Public Program 10/18-10/19/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Dynamics of Labor Negotiations 05W015 Public Program 10/31/0 5Henderson Cancelled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - L/M Strategies for Org Change 05W014 Public Program 10/25/05 Henderson Cancelled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Effective Collective Bargaining 05W013 Public Program 10/20-10/21/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Effective Discipline: Best 05W012 Public Program 9/14-9/15/95 Henderson Cancelled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Contract Language: Working 05W011 Public Program9/13/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Project Management Communication 05W009 Public Program 11/8-11/9/09 Henderson Canceled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Project Management Skills 05W008 Public Program 10/18-10/19/05 Henderson Cancelled, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 05W007 UAW-Ford NPC - Nashville Tn 10/31 - 11/4/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 05W006 UAW - Ford NPC- Detroit 10/17 - 10/21/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 05W005 UAW - Ford NPC Indy 9/26 - 9/30/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 05W004 UAW - Ford NPC - Black Lake MI 9/11 - 9/16/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 05W002 UAW - Ford NPC - Black Lake MI 7/25 - 7/29/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 05W001 UAW - Ford NPC - Black Lake MI 7/18 - 7/22/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - NYS Empire State Poll 2004 04W411B CU ILR Survey Research Institute 10/22/04 Fleron (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - AIS Participant Workbooks 04W410C UAW - Ford NPC January - April 2005 Fleron/Suggs (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Research + Modification 04W410D UAW - Ford NPC January - April 2005 Fleron/Suggs (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Audio Visual Updates 04W410B UAW - Ford NPC March 2005 Fleron/Suggs (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - AIS Participant Workbook 04W410A UAW - Ford NPC March 7, 2005 Fleron/Suggs (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - Labor Matters Posters 04W301 Fleron/Grogan, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Meetings 04W300 Erie County Association of School Boards Various Henderson, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - NYS Empire State Poll 2004 04W117 Public Program 12/14/04 Fleron (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - Economic Self Sufficiency 04W116 Communication/Advocacy Committee-Monthly Mtg 9/24/04-6/30/05 Fleron, 2004-2005 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - Crisis for Labor Movement 04W115 UALE / AFL-CIO 3/30/05 - 4/3/05 Fleron, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - Early Childhood Development 04W114 Federal Reserve Bank 3/3/05 Fleron, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Living Wage Commission Compliance 04W113A-D City of Buffalo 11/8/04; 3/10/05; 4/13/05; 4/21/05 Fleron, 2004-2005 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - CWA/ Child Care Coalition 04W112 WNY Legislative Delegation 9/16/04 Fleron, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - Writing Coach Services for R. Guinther 04W111 RSA Solutions Inc. 5/25/05 - 6/27/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - Security Officers for Columbia Univ 04W110 Cornell U - NYC Office 6/29/05 Henderson Race + Reconciliation Conference: Vision For the Future, 2000-2005 (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Race Reconciliation Conf 04W109 Public 5/26/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - Mgmt Adv Group Meeting 04W108 Planning Sesson 6/3/05 Rebholz/Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - Public Speaking-Effective Communication 04W107A/B Delaware North Companies 6/9/05 Rebholz, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - Interviewing and Selection 04W106 Delaware North Companies 5/16/05-5/23/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - Conversation with Senior Managers 04W105 Account Solutions Group 5/12/05 / Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - How to Interest Arbitration Really Works 04W104 Public Program May 20, 2005 Campagna (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - Conflict Resolution 04W103 GME Accounting May 5, 2005 Wheaton (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - Writing Services for Individuals 04W102 Mentholatum TBD Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - Preparation for Arbitration 04W100 UAWA 4601 6/3/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 59)
  - Life Style Mgmt Conf. 04W099 UAW - Ford NPC Noncredit 5/1 - 5/6/05 Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - Educational Leadership Conference 04W098 Rochesters Teachers Assoc 3/24/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 61)
  - Telecommunications Industry Workshop 04W097 Citizens Communications 4/27/05 Fleron, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 62)
  - Workplace Diversity: Stepping into 21st 04W096 ILR Resident 3/11; 3/12; 4/8; 4/9/05 Henderson/Woods, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 63)
  - Effective Grievance Handling 04W095 Chautauqua + Erie Telephone Co 4/19/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 64)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 04W094 UAW Ford NPC 4/11 - 4/15/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - CBTU - Mentee Program 04W092 CBTU Various Johnson, 2004-2005 (Box 79, Folder 66)
  - Leading to Pro Excellence 04W091 Account Solutions Group LLC 4/22/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 67)
  - Leading to Build Relationships 04W090 Account Solutions Group LLC 4/15/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 68)
  - Leading to Develop 04W089 Account Solutions Group LLC 4/1/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 69)
  - Leading for Pro Excellence 04W088 Account Solutions Group LLC 3/18/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 70)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 04W086 UAW - Ford NPC Greensboro, NC 6/6 - 6/10/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 71)
  - 2004 Economic Issues for Workers 04W085 WNY Area Labor Federation 9/4/04 + 10/16/06 Johnson (Box 79, Folder 72)
  - Labor History 04W084 Cement Masons 3/9/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 73)
  - Individual Coaching 04W083 Robert Fox 4/18/05 + 4/21/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 74)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 04W082 UAW - Ford NPC - Los Angles CA 4/25 - 4/29/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 75)
  - EMP Maintenance: AIS 04W081 UAW - Ford NPC - St Louis Mo 3/14-3/18/05 Fleron/Suggs, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 76)
- Program Files-Credit, Grad St.. (Box 80)
  - World Trade Center- BFLO/Niagara -1W098 Export New York 3/20/2002 Wheaton (Box 80, Folder 1)
    3 1/2 Inch Floppy Disk "Export NY ARS questions"
  - Veterans Administration 01W097 Successful Project Management 2/20/02 Mingus (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - OPEIU Local 212 01W096A Negotiation for a Health Future 2/02/02 Lipsitz, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Blue Cross + Blue Shield/ OPEIU 01W096B Negotiating for a Healthy Future 2/4/02 + 2/05/02 Campagna, et. Al, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Int'l. Assoc of Firefighters 01W095 IAFF 2002 Human Relations Conference 1/14/02 Suggs/ Woods, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - UAW - Ford NPC 01W094 Lifestyle Management - Train the Trainer 2/11/02-2/15/02 Woods/ Strusa/ Suggs, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Frontier Central School District 01W093 Interest Based Approach to Problem Solv January 25, 2002 Campagna (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Chautauqua Workforce Dev. Ctr. 01W092 Sexual Harassment/ Conflict Resolution 1/10/02 Wheaton, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Chautauqua Workforce Dev. Center 01W091 Sexual Harassment/ Conflict Resolution 1/8/02 Wheaton, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Recession, Manufacturing + Labor Move. 01W090 IUE District, AFL-CIO / CWA 2/11/02 Lipsitz, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Confect Resolution for Unionists 0IW089 USWA District 9 2/28/02 Lipsitz, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Mutual Gains 0IW088 Associated Spring Division 1/31/02 + 2/1/2002 Campagna Canc., 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - High Performance Workplace 0IW087B Harper International Corporation 1/22/02 + 1/23/02 Henderson, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Successful Project Mgmt. 0IW087A Harper International Corporation 1/8/02 + 1/9/02 Henderson, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Strikes: Strategy + Tactics 01W086 CWA 11417 12/19/01 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - High Road Economics 01W085 IBEW #31 12/13/01 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Supervisory Studies Advisory 01W084 12/12/01 Rebholz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Labor History 01W083 NYS United Teachers 10/12/01 - 10/14/01 Blair, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Public 01W082 ASID 2/18/02 - 4/29/02 Henderson, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Creative Problem Solving 01W081 Buffalo Municipal Housing Authority 12/1/01 Campagna, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - When Crisis Hits: Dealing w/ stress 01W080 Public 2/22/02 Lipsitz, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Web Design for Unionists 01W079 Buffalo Workforce Dev. Ctr / AFL/CIO 1/28/02 - 2/13/02 (6 sessions) Lipsitz, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - SHRM 01W076 Public 1/28 - 4/22/02 Henderson, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Registrations SHRM (Spring) 01W076, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Income + Expense Documentation SHRM (Spring) 01W076, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Running an Effective Meeting 01W077 Buffalo Municipal Housing Authority 11/24/01 Campagna, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Labor Unions + The Internet 01W078 Buffalo Workforce Dev. Ctr / AFL-CIO1/14/02, 1/16/02, 1/21/02, 1/23/02 Lipsitz, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Secretaries Day 01W075 Public 4/24/2002 Rbholz, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - SHRM On-line 01W074 Public 2/11/2002 - 4/29/2002 Henderson, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Train-the-Trainer-Adjunct Workshop 01W073 Adjunct Faculty 11/28/2002 Wheaton, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Recession + Impact on Living 01W072 CWA 14177 11/13/2002 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Federalizing the Airports 01W071 SEIU 200 United 10/22/01 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Buffalo Labor Programs: An Overview 01W070 National Assoc. of Letter Carriers #3 11/21/01 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Buffalo Housing Development 01W069 AFL-CIO Econ. Dev. Group 10/17/2001 Lipsitz (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Training Union Reps to Train Stewards 01W068 SEIU 1199 Upstate 11/8 + 11/9/2001 Lipsitz (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment 01W076A/B/C Carborundum Company 11/1/01 Henderson, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - New Era Strike Presentation 01W066 Behind the Labor Organization 10/23/01 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Employment Arbitration 01W065 IRRA for WNY 10/17/01 Campagna, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Introduction to H / R Law 01W058 Public 3/13/2002 Grogan (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - APA - Advanced Payroll Skills 01W064 Public 4/9/2002 - 6/18/2002 Grogan, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - APA - Essential Payroll Skills 01W063 Public 1/29/2002-3/19/2002 Grogan (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Investigatory Grievance 01W062 Public 5/2/2002 Grogan (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Discipline + Grievance Proc. 01W061 Public 4/20/2002 - 5/1/2002 Grogan (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Costing Out Coll. Barg. Agreement 01W060 Public 4/16/2002 Grogan (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - Prep. For Collective Bargaining 01W059 Public 4/15/2002 Grogan (Box 80, Folder 45)
- Faculty - Rebholz, Yvonne. (Box 81)
  - Graduation -SS, 1999-2001 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - H+ S Progs, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - H+S Brochure 7/00, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Healy, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Henderson, Pam (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Groat Award, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Historical Soc.- P...EC, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - ID Cards - Student, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - ADR for CR Prac 2-27-97, 1995-1997 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - IIS, 1994-1997 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Women + Work, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Women and Work, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Uniformed Seminars, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - EEO, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - AM AXLE - Communications, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - -98-99 Mgmt + L-M, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Open House 6/23/97, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - COLOSI- ADR, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Work Out, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Mgmt Progs S 98, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Marketing- Ads- General, 1987-1998 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Computer Stuff, 1994-1997 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Work Reorg., 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Program Tasks, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Assorted Docs: Adult Educational Services Committee, Docs. Related to Computers Etc., 1997-1999 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - EEOC - ADR Project, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Bflo Public Schools, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - GS- Canisius, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - World + Well-Being - '99 Conf. Delprino, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - TANF, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Softbank 4/28/98, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - HSC Controls, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - GS- Spring '98, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - American Axle "Career to Community", 1996-1998 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - GS Review (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - GS Review (Folder 2 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - GS Think Tank, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Supervisory Studies - 98, 1998-1999 (Box 81, Folder 38)
- administration-Program Files. (Box 82)
  - Graduate Studies - Winter 1993 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    One main folder contains other folders
  - Graduate Studies Program 92W123 Employment Discrim + Law (202-784-01) 1/5 - 3/23/93 Giroux, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Studies Program 92W124 Collective Bargaining (202-500-01) 1/6 - 3/24/93 Smith, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - "Theory + History": Articles related to Labor (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Articles/Readings Related to Labor and Unions, 1982-1989 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Articles/Readings Related to Collective Bargaining, Unions, Industry etc., 1980 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Articles/Readings Related to Collective Bargaining, Unions etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Articles/Readings Related to Collective Bargaining, Unions etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Studies - Spring 1993 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    Main folder contains other folders
  - Graduate Studies 92W136 Hum Res Econ + Pub Pol (761) 4/1 - 6/24/93 Davis, 1991-1993 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - GSCP-Spring 1993 - HUM Res Econ + PUB Pol Davis (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - GSCP-Spring 1993-Arbitration Bantle, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies - Fall 1992, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - BLS-Fall 1992 - Contract Admin. - Jurenovich, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - BLS-Fall 1992 - Contract Admin. - Moore (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - BLS-Fall 1992 - Labor History - Blair, 1987-1992 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - BLS-Fall 1992 - Conflict Resolution - Berkhoudt (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Program Files-Ils Credit. (Box 83)
  - IIS - UAW-Ford NEDTC S94 93I018 Employment Maintenance (230-052) LEC01 4/18/94 - 4/22/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - IIS - UAW-Ford NEDTC W94 93I017 Employment Maintenance (230-052) LEC01 3/21/94 - 3/25/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - IIS - Ford Motor Company 93I016 Auto Industry Dynamics 9/22/93 Blair, 1993-1994 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - IIS - Ford Motor Company 93I015 Auto Industry Dynamics 9/15/93 Blair, 1993-1994 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - IIS UAW-GM Human Resource Center 93I014 Regional PEL - "The Auto Ind. In Transition: 6/6-6/9/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - IIS UAW-GM Human Resource Center 93I013 Regional PEL- "The Auto Ind. In Transition" 5/2-5/5/94 Blair, 1993-1994 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - IIS UAW-GM Human Resource Center 93I012 Regional PEL - "The Auto Industry in Transition" 4/11-4/14/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - IIS UAW-GM Human Resource Center 93I011 Regional PEL - "The Auto Industry in Transition" 3/7-3/10/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - IIS-UAW GM Human Resource Center 93I008 Regional PEL: Auto Ind. In Transition 12/06/93-12/09/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - IIS - UAW-Human Resource Center 93I005 Regional PEL: Auto Ind. in Transition 7/19/93-7/22/93 Blair (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC F93 93I004 Employment Maintenance (230-052) LEC04 11/08/93-11/12/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC F93 93I003 Employment Maintenance (230-052) LEC03 10/25/93-10/29/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC F93 93I002 Employment Maintenance (230-052) LEC02 10/04/93-10/08/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC F93 93I001 Employment Maintenance (230-052) LEC01 08/09/93-08/13/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 92I027 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 06/21/93-06/25/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 92I026 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 5/24/93-5/28/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 92I025 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 5/10/93 - 5/14/93, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - IIS-Niagara Mohawk IBEW 92I024 Current Labor Relations Issues March 2, 1993 Blair + Woods (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - IIS-World University Games 92I023 Cultural Awareness + Customer Care 02/13/93 + 3/13/93 Henderson, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - IIS-Niagara Mohawk IBEW 92I022 Current Labor Relations Issues March 1, 1993 Blair+ Woods (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - IIS-UAW Ford NEDTC 92I016 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 2/22/93 - 2/26/93, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 92I015 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 1/11/93 - 1/15/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    Some documents folded in half
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I010 Employment Maintenance 6/14/93 - 6/17/93, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I008 Employment Maintenance 4/19/93 - 4/22/93, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I007 Employment Maintenance 3/15/93 - 3/18/93 CANCELLED, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I006 Employment Maintenance 2/15/93 - 2/18/93, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I002 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 1/25/93 - 1/28/93 Blair, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I005 Employment Maintenance 1/11/92 - 1/14/93 Cancelled, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I009 Employment Maintenance 5/17/93 - 5/20/93, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I004 Employment Maintenance 12/7/92 - 12/10/92, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 92I003 Employment Maintenance 11/9/92 - 11/12/92 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 91I013 Employment Maintenance 12/02/91 - 12/05/91, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 91I012 Employment Maintenance 11/04/91 - 11/07/91, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - IIS UAW-GM HRC, Region #9 91I011 Employment Maintenance 10/28/91 - 10/31/91, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 34)